MAXWELL HANKNER

Minneapolis, MN 55418 | (612) 978-5994 | maxwellhankner@gmail.com

Summary

Web developer with two years of experience in various web technologies. Coachable and great at brainstorming with coworkers but can also learn and problem solve independently. Committed to leveraging resources and learning quickly to overcome all challenges that arise in any work setting. A highly motivated individual who wants to help improve a company's technical operations.

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React

- Redux
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL

- AWS
- Github
- AdobeXD
- Photoshop

Work Experience

Web Developer / Freelancer - Minneapolis, MN January 2019 – Current

- Designed and created a website for an insurance claims business located in Bozeman,
 Montana.
- Set up multiple Google business accounts and improved SEO.
- Currently building an eCommerce store and integrating APIs for a client.

Smooth Moves LLC / Owner - Minneapolis, MN February 2017 - November 2019

- Owned and operated a furniture moving company in the Twin Cities metropolitan area.
- Oversaw all aspects of the business such as accounting, management, web presence/marketing, customer service, and scheduling.
- Hired and worked with an experienced web developer to create an internal dispatching application that allowed employees to pick up jobs and have access to job information.

Education

University of Minnesota / Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp - St. Paul, MN March 2020 – June 2020